Guide to the George B. Post Architectural Records and Drawings Collection PR 53
© 2011 New-York Historical Society
- Wisconsin State Capitol - Madison, WI
  - East Wing - electric work: 2nd floor plan; ink on linen, 1909-02-23 (Box 388)
  - East Wing - electric work: 3rd floor plan; ink on linen, 1909-02-23 (Box 388)
  - East Wing - electric work: attic floor plan; ink on linen, 1909-06-11 (Box 388)
  - East Wing - heat & vent: basement plan; ink on linen, 1915-02-24 (Box 388)
  - East Wing - basement plan; ink on linen, 1908-07-24 (Box 388)
  - East Wing - 1st floor plan; ink on linen, 1909-10-07 (Box 388)
  - East Wing - 2nd floor plan; ink on linen, 1915-05-19 (Box 388)
  - East Wing - 3rd floor plan; ink on linen, 1915-05-21 (Box 388)
  - East Wing - attic floor plan; ink on linen, 1909-05-27 (Box 388)
  - East Wing - section AA; ink on linen, 1915-05-18 (Box 388)
  - East Wing - main transverse section BB; ink on linen, 1915-05-18 (Box 388)
  - East Wing - transverse section C-C & D-D near west wall; ink on linen, 1908-07-24 (Box 388)
  - East Wing - longitudinal section E-E near north wall; ink on linen, 1909-10-07 (Box 388)
  - East Wing - transverse section F-F near east wall; ink on linen, 1915-05-21 (Box 388)
  - East Wing - steel framing for supreme court & main stair hall; ink on linen, 1908-07-25 (Box 388)
  - East Wing - plumbing system; ink on linen, 1908-07-24 (Box 388)
  - East Wing - structural: transverse sections C-C facing east wall, D-D facing west wall; ink on linen, 1908-07-07 (Box 388)
  - East Wing - structural: elevation & sections of west wall; ink on linen, 1915-05-18 (Box 388)
  - East Wing - column schedule & typical details; ink on linen, 1908-01-17 (Box 388)
  - East Wing - judges' studies, lobbies, toilets & secretaries' rooms, 2nd fl.; ink on linen, 1909-03-27 (Box 388)
  - East Wing - windows & radiator enclosures, 2nd fl.; ink on linen, 1908-09-15 (Box 388)
  - East Wing - windows & radiator enclosures, 3rd fl.; ink on linen, 1908-09-17 (Box 388)
  - East Wing - secondary stairs, toilets, etc. 2nd fl. / reading room, 3rd fl.; ink on linen, 1909-03-02 (Box 388)
  - East Wing - offices, closets, toilet rooms, etc. 3rd & attic floors; ink on linen, 1909-05-29 (Box 388)
  - East Wing - basement stairs, stair bet. 2nd fl. & 3rd fl. library, iron rail bet. exterior columns; ink on linen, 1915-05-20 (Box 388)
  - East Wing - ground floor plan; ink on linen, 1915-05-21 (Box 388)
  - Cross section of tunnel connecting the Capitol Heat and Power Plant with the State Capitol; ink on linen, 1909-05 (Box 388)
  - Ground floor plan showing connection bet. old dome & east wing; graphite on trace, 1908-07-15 (Box 388)
  - East Wing - fire back for chimneypiece in executive chamber; blueprint on paper, 1912-10-17 (Box 389)
  - South Wing - sketch showing tempering coils, air washer etc.; blueprint on paper (2 copies), 1915-03-10 (Box 389)
  - West Wing - sketch showing tempering coils, air washer etc.; blueprint on paper (2 copies), 1915-03-10 (Box 389)
  - East Wing - sketch showing tempering coils, air washer etc.; blueprint on paper (2 copies), 1915-03-10 (Box 389)
  - East Wing - change from brick to Kingford stone facing in executive chamber fireplace; blueprint on paper, 1913-03-03 (Box 389)
  - East Wing - revised plan of kitchen, serving room, butcher shop, store rooms, etc.; blueprint on paper (2 copies, 1915-02-26 (Box 389)
  - East Wing - 2nd floor plan; blueprint on paper (damaged), 1908-07-24 (Box 389)
  - East Wing - list of drawings #625 to #718, diagrams & details; 2 typewritten sheets adhered to manila paper (Box 389)
  - East Wing - section through ceiling light, room 407; ink on linen, 1909-08-26 (Box 389)
  - East Wing - riser diagram; ink on linen (Box 389)
  - East Wing - 1st fl. executive dept. new bathroom, scheme 1; graphite on trace, 1913-08-14 (Box 389)
  - East Wing - 1st fl. executive dept. new bathroom, scheme 2; graphite on trace, 1913-08-13 (Box 389)
  - East Wing - 1st fl. executive dept. new bathroom; graphite on trace, 1913-08-12 (Box 389)
  - East Wing - fire back for chimneypiece in executive chamber; graphite on trace, 1912-10-17 (Box 389)
  - West Wing - sketch showing tempering coils, air washer etc.; ink on linen, 1915-03-10 (Box 389)
  - East Wing - sketch showing tempering coils, air washer etc.; ink on linen, 1915-03-10 (Box 389)
  - South Wing - sketch showing tempering coils, air washer etc.; ink on linen, 1915-03-10 (Box 389)
  - East Wing - revised plan of kitchen, serving room, butcher shop, store rooms, etc.; ink on linen, 1915-02-26 (Box 389)
  - East Wing - revision of 2nd fl #603 & sections #606 & 607, new piers, transoms & revised floor tiling; graphite on trace, 1909-09-28 (Box 389)
  - Central Portion - section & elevation, interior of dome above grade level +72'; blueprint on linen, 1911-08-03 (Box 389)
  - Central Portion - interior finish, elevations & sections to level 91-5.5"; blueprint on linen, 1911-07-17 (Box 389)
  - Central Portion - interior finish, elevations & sections to level +107'; blueprint on linen, 1911-07-17 (Box 389)
  - Central Portion - interior finish, plans of 2nd, 3rd, attic ring course & dome; blueprint on linen, 1912-08-12 (Box 389)
  - Central Portion - interior finish, plans of basement, ground, & 1st fl.; blueprint on linen, 1911-07-17 (Box 389)
  - NW Pavilion - details of barber shop; graphite on trace, 1915-07-03 (Box 389)
  - North Wing - jointing of stones for statuary in itympanum of pediment; ink on linen, 1913-10-23 (Box 389)
  - Central Portion - elevations, sections & plan of dome section showing cut stone work & part of approaches; graphite on trace (damaged), 1906-12-24 (Box 389)
  - Central Portion - plans, sections & elevation of dome & entrance pavilions & approaches showing exterior cut stone work; ink on linen, 1908-01-30 (Box 389)
  - Central Portion - NE & NW corner pavilions, sections & elevations; ink on linen, 1913-04-18 (Box 389)
  - Central Portion - corner pavilions, ground floor diagrams & details; ink on linen, 1914-02-04 (Box 389)
  - Central Portion - corner pavilions, diagrams & details of 1st-3rd & attic floors; ink on linen, 1914-02-04 (Box 389)
  - Central Portion - scale diagrams & details of doors & windows; ink on linen, 1913-07-08 (Box 389)
  - Central Portion - dimension plans of finished wall surfaces of basement, ground, 1st & 2nd floors; ink on linen, 1914-04-11 (Box 389)
  - Central Portion - SW corner pavilion, diagrams & details of 2nd fl.; ink on linen, 1912-12-02 (Box 389)
  - Central Portion - corner pavilions, sections & elevations; ink on linen, 1914-09-16 (Box 389)
  - Central Portion - 3rd floor plan, heating & electric work; ink on linen, 1912-03-05 (Box 389)
  - Central Portion - attic floor plan, heating & electric work; ink on linen, 1914-04-10 (Box 389)
  - Central Portion - reflector & riser diagrams, electric work; ink on linen, 1912-03-05 (Box 389)
  - Central Portion - NE & NW corner pavilions. structural: 2nd, 3rd, attic & roof plans; ink on linen, 1913-04-17 (Box 390)
  - Central Portion - SE & SW corner pavilions. heat & vent: basement, ground, 1st, 2nd, 3rd & attic floor plans; ink on linen (Box 390)
  - South Wing and Central Portion - SE & SW corner pavilions. basement floor plans; ink on linen, 1911-11-10 (Box 390)
  - Central Portion - SE & SW corner pavilions. ground, 1st, 2nd, 3rd & attic floor plans; ink on linen, 1911-11-10 (Box 390)
  - Central Portion - corner pavilions. basement plan, part ground floor plan & section thro' toilet; ink on linen, 1915-02-24 (Box 390)
  - Central Portion - corner pavilions. ground, 1st, 2nd, 3rd & attic plans; ink on linen, 1914-09-16 (Box 390)
  - Central Portion - NE & NW corner pavilions. structural: ground & 1st floor plans; ink on linen, 1913-04-17 (Box 390)
  - Central Portion - statuary groups at base of dome; ink on linen, 1912-07-09 (Box 390)
  - Central Portion - NE & NW corner pavilions. steps, balustrade & entrance porches; ink on linen, 1913-04-20 (Box 390)
  - Central Portion - NE & NW corner pavilion plans; ink on linen, 1913-04-20 (Box 390)
  - Central Portion - NE & NW corner pavilions. exterior walls & sections; ink on linen, 1913-04-19 (Box 390)
  - Central Portion - heat & electric: ring course plan at E-E; ink on linen, 1914-04-23 (Box 390)
  - Central Portion - heat & electric: plan at FF, II, KK, MM & NN; ink on linen, 1912-03-05 (Box 390)
  - Central Portion - NE & NW corner pavilions. structural: foundation & basement plans; ink on linen, 1913-04-18 (Box 390)
  - Central Portion - interior finish. plans of 2nd, 3rd, attic ring course & dome; ink on linen, 1911-07-17 (Box 390)
  - Central Portion - 1st contract: structural 2nd floor plan, 2nd contract: columns & girders supporting superstructure of dome; ink on linen, 1910-02-28 (Box 390)
  - Central Portion - 1st contract, structural: 3rd & attic floors & ring course plans, 2nd contract: columns & girders supporting super structure of dome; ink on linen, 1910-02-28 (Box 390)
  - Central Portion - 1st contract: elevations & sections of piers & walls, 2nd contract: columns & girders supporting superstructure of dome; ink on linen
  - Central Portion - structural: courses & jointing of pier RSTU & R'S'T'U'; ink on linen, 1909-05-11 (Box 390)
  - Central Portion - 1st contract, structural: podium wall plans, elevations & sections. 2nd contract: columns & girders supporting superstructure of dome; ink on linen, 1910-02-28 (Box 390)
  - Central Portion - SE & SW corner pavilions & steps. excavation plan; ink on linen, 1909-07-07 (Box 390)
  - Central Portion - NE & NW corner pavilions. heat & vent., electric: basement & ground plans; ink on linen, 1915-02-24 (Box 390)
  - Central Portion - NE & NW corner pavilions. heat & vent., electric: 1st, 2nd, 3rd & attic plans; ink on linen, 1914-10-05 (Box 390)
  - Central Portion - skylights on roof of podium wall; ink on linen, 1911-01-30 (Box 390)
  - Central Portion - superstructure: window frames, kalamain door & door frames, circular stair landing & window guards in lantern; ink on linen, 1914-04-27 (Box 390)
  - Central Portion - frames & louvres at fresh air intakes, podium roof & louvres in lantern; ink on linen, 1911-10-21 (Box 390)
  - Central Portion - interior finish, scale diagrams of arches & pendentives; ink on linen
  - Central Portion - columns & pilasters, 1st floor of rotunda; graphite on trace, 1913-10-22 (Box 390)
  - Central Portion - heating & electric: ground floor plan; ink on linen, 1912-03-05 (Box 390)
  - Central Portion - heating & electric: 1st floor plan; ink on linen, 1912-03-05 (Box 390)
  - Central Portion - heating & electric: 2nd floor plan; ink on linen, 1912-03-05 (Box 390)
  - Central Portion - section & elevation of interior of dome; ink on linen, 1911-08-03 (Box 390)
  - Central Portion - heating & electric: basement floor plan; ink on linen, 1912-03-05 (Box 390)
  - Central Portion - interior finish: elevations & sections to level 107'; ink on linen, 1911-07-17 (Box 390)
  - Central Portion - interior finish: elevations & sections to level 91-5.5"; ink on linen, 1912-08-12 (Box 390)
  - Central Portion - 1st contract: plans for foundations for piers & walls. 2nd contract: columns & girders supporting superstructure of dome; ink on linen, 1910-02-28 (Box 390)
  - Central Portion - 1st contract: structural ground floor plan. 2nd contract: columns & girders supporting the superstructure of the dome; ink on linen, 1914-02-02 (Box 390)
  - Central Portion - 1st contract: structural 1st floor plan. 2nd contract: columns & girders supporting superstructure of dome; ink on linen, 1910-02-28 (Box 390)
  - Central Portion - structural: plans of superstructure showing top of podium wall, roof & drum with peristyle; ink on linen, 1911-06-23 (Box 390)
  - Central Portion - structural: plans of superstructure showing attic, base & dome, lantern; ink on linen, 1911-03-22 (Box 390)
  - Central Portion - structural: section of superstructure showing balustrade, podium wall, etc.; ink on linen, 1911-10-23 (Box 390)
  - Central Portion - structural: elevation & section of superstructure showing balustrade of podium wall, drum with peristyle, etc.; ink on linen, 1911-10-31 (Box 390)
  - Central Portion - structural: elevations & sections, superstructure of dome; ink on linen, 1915-02-27 (Box 390)
  - Central Portion - structural: elevations & sections of dome & lantern; ink on linen, 1915-02-27 (Box 390)
  - Central Portion - granite work for 4 groups of statuary on pedestals at base of dome; ink on linen, 1910-07-11 (Box 391)
  - Central Portion - interior finish: plans of basement, ground, & 1st floor; ink on linen, 1913-10-23 (Box 391)
  - Basement floor plan assignment; ink on linen, 1914-05-12 (Box 391)
  - Gound floor plan assignment; ink on linen, 1914-05-12 (Box 391)
  - First floor plan assignment; ink on linen, 1914-05-12 (Box 391)
  - Second floor plan assignment; ink on linen, 1914-05-12 (Box 391)
  - Third floor plan assignment; ink on linen, 1914-05-12 (Box 391)
  - Attic floor plan assignment; ink on linen, 1914-05-12 (Box 391)
  - Central Portion - structural: dome framing above grade 173'8"; ink on linen, 1911-11-03 (Box 391)
  - Central Portion - structural: dome framing btwn grades 145'10" & 203'; ink on linen, 1910-06-29 (Box 391)
  - Central Portion - half plans for terra cotta floor arches below level 78'10"; ink on linen, 1914-02-02 (Box 391)
  - Central Portion - structural: columns & girders above grade 78', dome superstructure; ink on linen, 1910-06-29 (Box 391)
  - Central Portion - 2nd contract: columns & girders below grade 78' supporting superstructure of dome; ink on linen, 1910-02-28 (Box 391)
  - Central Portion - elevation & section of superstructure showing podium wall adjacent to wings, etc.; ink on linen, 1909-05-24 (Box 391)
  - Central Portion - structural: temporary enclosure & roof; ink on linen, 1909-07-13 (Box 391)
  - North Wing - structural: roof plan; ink on linen, 1913-08-25 (Box 391)
  - North Wing - structural: north end elevation; ink on linen, 1913-03-04 (Box 391)
  - North Wing - west elevation, east elevation same reversed; ink on linen, 1913-04-23 (Box 391)
  - North Wing - structural: main longitudinal section A-A; ink on linen, 1914-01-07 (Box 391)
  - North Wing - structural: main transverse, section B-B; ink on linen, 1913-03-27 (Box 391)
  - North Wing - structural, transverse sections: C-C facing north wall, D-D facing south wall; ink on linen, 1913-11-19 (Box 391)
  - North Wing - east & west end elevations, exterior cut stone work; ink on linen, 1913-03-05 (Box 391)
  - North Wing - north end elevation cut stone work; ink on linen, 1913-03-05 (Box 391)
  - North Wing - structural: column schedules & typical details; ink on linen, 1913-03-27 (Box 391)
  - North Wing - window frames, attic exterior door, recesses for radiators under windows; ink on linen, 1913-04-24 (Box 391)
  - North Wing - structural: framing of main stairs & landing; ink on linen, 1913-03-27 (Box 391)
  - North Wing - longitudinal section A-A; ink on linen, 1915-07-06 (Box 391)
  - North Wing - structural: attic floor plan; ink on linen, 1913-03-27 (Box 391)
  - North Wing - structural: 3rd floor plan; ink on linen, 1913-03-27 (Box 391)
  - North Wing - structural: 2nd floor plan; ink on linen, 1913-11-26 (Box 391)
  - North Wing - structural: 1st floor plan; ink on linen, 1913-11-26 (Box 391)
  - North Wing - structural: ground floor plan; ink on linen, 1913-11-26 (Box 391)
  - North Wing - structural: basement plan, foundation & grillage; ink on linen, 1914-07-09 (Box 391)
  - North Wing - structural: excavation plan & north terrace plan; ink on linen, 1913-04-26 (Box 391)
  - North Wing - minor stair case btwn ground & first floors; ink on linen, 1914-09-01 (Box 391)
  - North Wing - schedule & electric fixtures; ink on linen, 1914-03-29 (Box 391)
  - Electric light fixtures & schedule; blueprint on paper, 1914-03-29 (Box 391)
  - North Wing - ceiling lights for 3rd & attic floors; ink on linen, 1914-09-28 (Box 391)
  - North Wing - heat & vent: radiator enclosures; ink on linen, 1914-09-05 (Box 391)
  - North Wing - finish of principal offices & main corridor; ink on linen, 1914-09-02 (Box 391)
  - North Wing - hardware for grille doors to main stair corridors & elevators; ink on linen, 1908-12-09 (Box 391)
  - North Wing - toilet, coat, rest, & locker rooms; ink on linen, 1915--01-07 (Box 391)
  - North Wing - finish of rooms, offices, closets & corridors; ink on linen, 1914-08-06 (Box 391)
  - North Wing - main transverse section B-B; ink on linen, 1915-01-06 (Box 391)
  - North Wing - distribution boxes; ink on linen, 1915-03-15 (Box 391)
  - North Wing - sketch of measurements of projections from wall line in pediment; graphite on manila (Box 391)
  - North Wing - NW corner pavilion: arrangement of toilets for public & employees; blueprint on paper, 1913-09-20 (Box 391)
  - North Wing - jointing of stones for statuary in tympanum of pediment; blueprint on paper, 1913-10-09 (Box 391)
  - North Wing - NW pavilion: basement rooms & barber shop; ink on linen, 1914-09-01 (Box 392)
  - North Wing - offices & corridors, ground floor; ink on linen, 1915-01-07 (Box 392)
  - North Wing - windows & radiator enclosures, ground & 1st floors; ink on linen, 1915-05-03 (Box 392)
  - North Wing - 1st floor corridors & stair galleries; ink on linen, 1914-08-03 (Box 392)
  - North Wing - 1st floor: offices, closets, locker & toilet rooms, corridors; ink on linen, 1915-01-07 (Box 392)
  - North Wing - main offices 1st fl., bank examiner's & state engineer's depts.; ink on linen, 1915-01-07 (Box 392)
  - North Wing - main offices 1st fl., supt. of public instruction; ink on linen, 1915-01-07 (Box 392)
  - North Wing - scale diagram of audience room & lobby, 2nd fl.; ink on linen, 1915-09-14 (Box 392)
  - North Wing - 2nd, 3rd & attic floors: offices, corridors & toilet rooms; ink on linen, 1914-11-09 (Box 392)
  - North Wing - 2nd, 3rd, & attic floors: windows & radiator enclosures; ink on linen, 1914-08-06 (Box 392)
  - North Wing - 3rd & attic floors: offices, corridors & toilet rooms; ink on linen, 1914-11-10 (Box 392)
  - North Wing - 2nd & 3rd floors: corridors & stair galleries; ink on linen, 1914-08-07 (Box 392)
  - North Wing - basement plan; ink on linen, 1914-09-07 (Box 392)
  - North Wing - ground floor plan; ink on linen, 1914-12-15 (Box 392)
  - North Wing - 1st floor plan; ink on linen, 1914-12-14 (Box 392)
  - North Wing - 2nd floor plan; ink on linen, 1915-01-06 (Box 392)
  - North Wing - 3rd floor plan; ink on linen, 1915-01-06 (Box 392)
  - North Wing - attic floor plan; ink on linen, 1915-03-15 (Box 392)
  - North Wing - transverse section C-C & D-D; ink on linen, 1915-01-06 (Box 392)
  - North Wing - longitudinal section E-E; ink on linen, 1914-09-07 (Box 392)
  - North Wing - transverse section F-F; ink on linen, 1914-09-07 (Box 392)
  - North Wing - plumbing work; ink on linen, 1915-01-15 (Box 392)
  - North Wing - electric lighting: basement plan; ink on linen, 1915-01-14 (Box 392)
  - North Wing - electric lighting: ground floor plan; ink on linen, 1915-01-14 (Box 392)
  - North Wing - electric lighting: 1st floor plan; ink on linen, 1915-01-14 (Box 392)
  - North Wing - electric lighting: 2nd floor plan; ink on linen, 1915-07-28 (Box 392)
  - North Wing - electric lighting: 3rd floor plan; ink on linen, 1915-01-14 (Box 392)
  - North Wing - electric lighting: attic plan; ink on linen, 1915-01-15 (Box 392)
  - North Wing - electric lighting: search light & electric riser diagram; ink on linen, 1914-10-05 (Box 392)
  - North Wing - heat & vent: basement plan; ink on linen, 1915-06-10 (Box 392)
  - North Wing - heat & vent: ground floor plan; ink on linen, 1914-10-06 (Box 392)
  - North Wing - heat & vent: 1st floor plan; ink on linen, 1915-01-07 (Box 392)
  - North Wing - heat & vent: 2nd floor plan; ink on linen, 1914-12-12 (Box 392)
  - North Wing - heat & vent: 3rd floor plan; ink on linen, 1914-10-06 (Box 392)
  - North Wing - heat & vent: attic floor plan; ink on linen, 1915-07-06 (Box 392)
  - North Wing - heat & vent: steam riser diagram; ink on linen, 1914-10-06 (Box 392)
  - North Wing - doors to rooms, closets, etc. (except front & revolving); ink on linen, 1914-09-01 (Box 392)
  - North Wing - G.A.R. Memorial Hall, attic floor; ink on linen, 1914-09-28 (Box 392)
  - North Wing - basement stairs under secondary stairs; ink on linen, 1914-07-25 (Box 392)
  - North Wing - frames for elevator fronts; ink on linen, 1914-08-07 (Box 392)
  - North Wing - end of barrel vault, main stairs & ornament crowning pediment; ink on linen, 1914-08-07 (Box 392)
  - North Wing - ground floor plan, preliminary study; graphite on trace (damaged), 1912-10-07 (Box 392)
  - North Wing - 1st floor plan, preliminary study; graphite on trace (damaged) (Box 392)
  - North Wing - 2nd floor plan, preliminary study; graphite on trace (damaged), 1912-10-07 (Box 392)
  - North Wing - sketch of 2nd floor plan; graphite on trace (damaged)
  - North Wing - 3rd floor plan, preliminary study; graphite on trace (damaged), 1912-10-07 (Box 392)
  - North Wing - attic floor plan, preliminary study; graphite on trace (damaged), 1912-10-07 (Box 392)
  - North Wing - north wall of lobby of audience room. revised entrance & cornice; graphite on trace, 1915-03-24 (Box 392)
  - North Wing - NE pavilion: 2nd floor, revised sketch; graphite on trace, 1914-02-04 (Box 392)
  - NE pavilion, 2nd floor. court reporter assistant; graphite on trace, 1914-01-02 (Box 392)
  - NE pavilion, 3rd floor. revisor of statutes, 1914-01-02 (Box 392)
  - North Wing - NW pavilion: study of bath rooms, toilet rooms & barber shop in basement; graphite on trace, 1913-08-22 (Box 392)
  - North Wing - NW pavilion: study of bath rooms, toilet rooms & barber shop in basement; blueprint on paper, 1913-08-22 (Box 391)
  - North Wing - details of wood partition in room #212; graphite on trace, 1916-11-02 (Box 392)
  - North Wing - plan of west end of G.A.R. Memorial Hall with change to accommodate metal cases; graphite on trace, 1916-01-22 (Box 392)
  - West Wing - 2nd floor: finish of small offices, coat & toilet rooms; ink on linen, 1908-04-08 (Box 393)
  - West Wing - committee rooms, closets & toilet rooms on 3rd floor. finish on attic floor; ink on linen, 1908-04-09 (Box 393)
  - West Wing - desks for speaker, clerks & reporters; ink on linen, 1908-07-28 (Box 393)
  - West Wing - assembly parlor; ink on linen, 1908-05-20 (Box 393)
  - West Wing - toilet & coat rooms, all floors; ink on linen, 1908-05-28 (Box 393)
  - West Wing - floors of minor corridors, secondary stair halls, etc.; ink on linen, 1908-05-29 (Box 393)
  - West Wing - revised floor tiling plans showing marble work; ink on linen, 1908-06-19 (Box 393)
  - West Wing - main stair hall staircase & galleries; ink on linen, 1908-03-19 (Box 393)
  - West Wing - offices & office corridors, ground floor; ink on linen, 1908-04-06 (Box 393)
  - West Wing - 1st floor corridors & stair galleries; ink on linen, 1908-03-31 (Box 393)
  - West Wing - 3rd floor plan; ink on linen, 1909-03-30 (Box 393)
  - West Wing - attic plan; ink on linen, 1907-12-17 (Box 393)
  - West Wing - main longitudinal section A-A; ink on linen, 1907-12-18 (Box 393)
  - West Wing - main transverse section B-B; ink on linen, 1907-12-18 (Box 393)
  - West Wing - transverse section C-C, D-D (near east wall); ink on linen, 1907-12-18 (Box 393)
  - West Wing - basement floor plan; ink on linen, 1909-03-30 (Box 393)
  - West Wing - ground floor plan; ink on linen, 1914-03-23 (Box 393)
  - West Wing - longitudinal section E-E (near south wall); ink on linen, 1907-12-18 (Box 393)
  - West Wing - transverse section F-F (near west wall); ink on linen, 1907-12-18 (Box 393)
  - West Wing - 1st floor plan; ink on linen, 1909-03-30 (Box 393)